In a world where deception and power rules,
one brave woman answers the call of the people.
I think I'm going to run for office.
And ventures to the nation's capital
to bring a trusted voice to the halls of democracy.
I mean, if I ran, do you think you would vote for me?
It depends.
Oh, it depends.
I came through because I wanted to get some insight
from some folks who are already on the inside.
And, uh...
All you Afro is needed here.
No one is going to believe me in this.
You know what?
You never told me, what are you running for?
The question really is, what are we running to?
I'm running to the people.
How well do you think you know government?
I went to school.
I can answer a couple questions.
How are you fighting the colonization?
Are you doing martial arts?
If I were in any office,
it's from alderman to state senator to Republican.
Ooh.
What Satan just flew into my mouth?
The Santas came in here, right?
That's what happened.
I'll act that.
In Amanda We Trust,
an unapologetically political comedy doc
from Amanda Seals,
coming soon to the internet.
Hear that motorcade?
That's Kamala going home.
That could be me.
In AmandaWeTrust.com.
What?